Guide to the Joseph L. Fisher papers, 1930s-1992
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 1: U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1992
  - Ted Taylor seminar tax reform, February 14, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Tax reform act of 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Tax reform act of 1976, correspondence, October 1977 - January 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Tax reform act of 1976, correspondence, February - August 1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means carryover basis, correspondence, June - December 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Ways and means carryover basis, correspondence, January - July 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Tax reform act of 1976 (carryover basis), correspondence, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Carryover basis, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Tax reform of 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Tax reform act of 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ways and means committee tax reform, correspondence, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ways and means committee tax reform., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Freshman democrats tax reform committee, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Regulatory reform, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ways and means committee tax reduction act, March - December 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Ways and means committee tax reduction act, January - March 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tax simplification, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means committee tax simplification, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means committee tax shelters, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Tax shelters, minimum tax and allocation of deductions, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Tax shelters, minimum tax and allocation of deductions, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Charitable contributions, correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Fisher, conable, press releases, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fisher, conable, March - June 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Charitable contributions, tax exempt organizations, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Charitable contributions, tax exempt organizations, correspondence, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Charitable organizations, correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Charitable organizations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means committee charitable contributions, non-profit organizations, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Utility tax deduction bill, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Tuition tax credit, correspondence, January - March 1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Tuition tax credit, correspondence, May 16, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Tuition tax credit, correspondence, April - October 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Disability, sick pay exclusion, correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Disability, sick pay exclusion, correspondence, March - May 1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Disability, sick pay exclusion, correspondence, February 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Disability, sick pay exclusion, correspondence, January 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Tax credit for the elderly, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Tax credit for the elderly, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Retirement income credit, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ways and means retirement income credit, federal pension, correspondence, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means retirement income credit, federal pension, correspondence, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Retirement income credit, correspondence, October 13, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Retirement income credit, correspondence, October 13, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Retirement income credit, correspondence, February - March 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Tax-exempt bonds #1, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Tax-exempt bonds #2., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means committee deduction for utility taxes, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Capital formation, correspondence, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Capital formation task force, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Capital formation for "Little Guy" savings / ESOPS / Pensions, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Capital formation for "Little Guy" savings / ESOPS / Pensions, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Independent contractor, correspondence, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Tax relief for renters, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Deductions for renters, April 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Tax relief for renters, correspondence, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tax relief for renters, June 4, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Tax credit for renters, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Tenants, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Tenants tax relief bill, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Capital gains on foreigners, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Capital gains tax on foreigners, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Savings and loan issues, correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Business, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Small business, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Small business material, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 6877 small business, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Tax treatment of small business investment companies, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Capital gains, correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Groom bill, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Tax treatments of Americans living abroad, correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Taxation of foreign income, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Taxation of foreign income, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Tax of foreign income, correspondence, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Withholding tax on dividends and interest, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Capital cost recovery, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Capital cost recovery, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means committee, capital investment, corporate income, correspondence, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means committee, capital investment, corporate income, correspondence, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Tomaro (condominiums), correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Tomaro (condominiums), 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Condominium conversion seminar, correspondence, October 22, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Condominium conversion seminar, October 22, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Ways and means committee taxation on condominium associations, correspondence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sale of residence, correspondence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - IRS proposed regulations on dwellings, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Noisy aircraft revenue and credit act of 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 96th Congress, Fisher bill H.R. 8231, payments in lieu of taxes, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mortgage revenue bonds H.R. 3712, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Local property tax, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Ted Taylor seminars condominium conversions seminar, October 22, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Tax treatment of single taxpayers, correspondence, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Ways and means committee tax treatment of single persons, correspondence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Ways and means committee tax treatment of single persons, correspondence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Married / single taxpayers, correspondence, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Marriage penalty tax, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Tax treatment of married couples, correspondence, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means committee tax treatment of two-earner families, correspondence, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Ways and means committee tax treatment of two-earner families, correspondence, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Tax exempt status (private schools) who engage in racial discriminatory practices, correspondence, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Tax break for tuition, correspondence, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fisher estate tax bill, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Fisher estate tax bill, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Ways and means committee estate tax, correspondence, November - December 1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ways and means committee estate tax, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means committee disability tax exemptions, correspondence, September 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means committee disability tax exemptions, correspondence, October 1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Real wage insurance, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Disability pay exclusion, letter, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Disability / sick pay, correspondence, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Real wage insurance, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - National health insurance and cost containment, correspondence, June - August 1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - National health insurance and cost containment, correspondence, January - May 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means committee pensions / IRAs / KEOGH, correspondence, January 1975 - April 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Corman-Fisher modified I.R.A. bill, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Ways and means committee child care / Dependent care, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Taxes - Day care center, correspondence, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Ted Taylor seminar hospital cost containment seminar, April 17, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - National health insurance and cost containment, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means committee estate tax, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Pension, profit-sharing, etc., correspondence, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Pension, profit - S, H.R. 10, IRA etc, correspondence, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Ways and means committee pensions / IRAs / KEOGH, correspondence, May - December 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Humphrey-Hawkins bill, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Issues - unemployment, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Energy, 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Energy, correspondence, September - October 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Energy, correspondence, August 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Energy, correspondence, January - July 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Energy, correspondence, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Ways and means, energy, correspondence, January - February 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Ways and means, energy, correspondence, March 1975 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means, energy, correspondence, April 1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means, energy, correspondence, May 1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Ways and means, energy, correspondence, June 1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means, energy, correspondence, July - September 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Energy, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ted Taylor seminar energy, tax aspects, June 13, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ad hoc energy committee, correspondence, April - May 1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Ad hoc energy committee, correspondence, June 1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ad hoc energy committee, correspondence, August 1977 - January 1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Energy trust fund part I, January - August 1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Energy trust fund part I, September 1979 - March 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Energy trust fund part II, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Energy trust fund part III, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Energy trust fund part IV, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Energy tax of 1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Energy tax of 1977 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means committee, correspondence regarding H.R. 6860, Energy conservation bill, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Energy - miscellaneous: Gasahol, Thermostats, Moody Mobile, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Gasoline, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Gasoline rationing material, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Oil, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Oil import fee, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Synfuels, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Co-generational material, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - O'Leary meeting on gasoline, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Commuter tax, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Energy mobilization board, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Windfall profits tax H.R. 3919 part I, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Windfall profits tax, press, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Background information on windfall profits tax legislation part II, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Background information on windfall profits tax legislation part II, reports, copies of bill and committee, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Chrystler loan guarantees, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Chrystler loan guarantees, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Gas guzzler tax amendment, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Conservation easement, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Environment, issues, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Superfund (clearing up toxic waste) I, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Superfund (clearing up toxic waste) II, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Pollution excise taxes, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Taxes on pollution, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Taxes on pollution, July 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - D.C. professionals tax, correspondence, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - D.C. professionals tax, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Ways and means committee, Williamsburg bill, correspondence, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk and western bill, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Merchant marine bill, memo, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Airplane tax bill, correspondence, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Adoption bill, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Professional sports select subcommittee part I, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Professional sports select subcommittee part II, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Professional sports, correspondence, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - World peace tax fund, correspondence, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - World peace tax fund, correspondence, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Ways and means committee world peace tax fund bill, correspondence, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Trade, commodities meat, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Ways and means: Trade Eastern European trip, correspondence, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means: Trade Czechoslovakian gold, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means: Trade miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ted Taylor seminar multination trade negotiations, February 26, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Ted Taylor seminar trade, correspondence, May 9, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Ways and means public assistance, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Welfare, newspaper clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means: Trade adjustment assistance, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - MTNs Ted Taylor seminar, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Speech at international management and development institute, February 6, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Trade: Commodities sugar, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Issues, trade, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Ways and means regarding welfare and social security insurance, correspondence, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Ways and means public assistance, correspondence, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Ways and means welfare reform, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Ways and means regarding welfare and public assistance, correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Ways and means public assistance, correspondence, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Ways and means regarding social security disability, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Ted Taylor seminars social security disability insurance, March 12, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Ways and means universal coverage, correspondence, January - April 1979 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Ways and means universal coverage, correspondence, May - December 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means social security, correspondence, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means social security H.R. 9346, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Ways and means social security, newspaper clippings, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Ways and means social security, correspondence, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Ways and means social security, correspondence, October 21, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means social security, correspondence, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means social security, correspondence, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Ways and means Fisher amendment to social security H.R. 9346, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Ways and means Fisher amendment to social security H.R. 9346, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Ways and means Fisher amendment to social security H.R. 9346, correspondence, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means social security and civil service retirement, correspondence, October 5, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means social security, correspondence, September 21, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Budget, miscellaneous #1, correspondence, March - August 1979 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Budget, miscellaneous #2, correspondence, January - February 1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Budget resolution fiscal year 1980, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Reconciliation tax matters, report, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Reconciliation tax materials, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Census appointments #1, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Census appointments #2, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Appropriations bill material, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - First budget resolution for fiscal year 1981, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Budget committee, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Anti-inflation group and bill, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Inflation, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Budget committee, 1975-1980 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Budget, newspaper clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Fisher substitute to second budget resolution for fiscal year 1980 (never offered), 1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Budget letters, January - June 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Budget letters, July - November 1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Budget committee art's letters, correspondence, January - November 1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Budget committee art's letters, correspondence, December 1978 - January 1979 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - The government and economy, inflation, newspaper clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - The government and economy, articles, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Inflation, press, analysis, reports, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Inflation, press, analysis, reports, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Congressional proposals on inflation, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Budget projections, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Budget committee state of economy reports, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Ted Taylor seminar economy, January 4, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Ted Taylor seminar B-1 bomber, April 19, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - IRS appropriations amendment, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Budget: JLF amendment dollar information, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Armed services regarding divorced spouses, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Post offices and civil service regarding cost of living twice yearly, newspaper clippings, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Earth Day, post office and civil service, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Federal employees, 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Post office and civil service pay delays, correspondence, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Post office and civil service regarding federal pay, correspondence, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Post office and civil service federal compensation, correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Post office and civil service regarding reorganization, correspondence, January - April 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Post office and civil service regarding reorganization, correspondence, May - June 1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Post office and civil service regarding reorganization, correspondence, July - August 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Post office and civil service regarding civil service reorganization, correspondence, October - December 1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Post office and civil service regarding civil service reorganization, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Post office and civil service regarding civil service reform, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Post office and civil service regarding retires cost of living raise, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Civil service report, correspondence, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Federal employees, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, cover letter, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, correspondence, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, correspondence, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, correspondence, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Post office and civil service committee employee political rights information, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Post office and civil service committee employee political rights information, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Post office and civil service regarding federal retirement, correspondence, January - July 1977 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Post office and civil service regarding federal retirement, cover letter, May - June 1976 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Post office and civil service regarding federal retirement, June 28, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Post office and civil service regarding federal retirement, September 28, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Post office and civil service employee political rights, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Post office and civil service 1% factor, correspondence, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act Maryland, correspondence, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, June 15, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, June 15, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Post office and civil service regarding hatch act, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Indochina refugees, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Ted Taylor seminars Indochinese refugees, February 12, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Ted Taylor seminar Indochinese refuge seminar, February 12, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Defence votes, originals, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Defense and military, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Foreign policy, 1975-1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Diplomatic immunity (Jean McDonald from Mikki), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - International relations, diplomatic immunity, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - International relations, diplomatic immunity, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - International relations, diplomatic immunity, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Diplomacy, newspaper clippings and editorials, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Ted Taylor seminar international relations regarding Panama Canal, September 26, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Ted Taylor seminar Panama treaty seminar, September 26, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Diplomatic immunity, press release, newspaper clippings, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - McGuire, Scott, diplomatic immunity, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Liability insurance for diplomats, correspondence, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 1484 - diplomatic immunity, newspaper clippings, editorials, press releases, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Ted Taylor seminar undocumented aliens seminar, October 17, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Judiciary committee regarding illegal aliens (Ted Taylor seminar), 1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Issues, criminal justice, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax city reimbursement, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Judiciary Fairfax City, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Judiciary Fairfax City, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Judiciary committee civil and constitutional rights subcommittee, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - 95th and 94th Congress, abortion, 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - The encouraging bill, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Judiciary alternative to abortion, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Judiciary alternative to abortion, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Judiciary alternative to abortion, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Fair housing, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Judiciary, speech on patents, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - HEW kidney dialysis, newspaper clippings, correspondence, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Bilingual education, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Education, issue paper #7, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)